A Guide to the Great Falls Historical Society, Virginia Collection, c.1960s-2022
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 8: Photographic Materials, c.1960s -2001
  - Sub-series 8-2: Negatives, c.1960s-2001
    - Great Falls Park Old Merry-Go-Round 1890s(?), Undated
    - Great Falls Inn Postcard, Undated
    - Norman Bradford Collection, Harrison Jenkins reunion at Dranesville Tavern 1923, Undated
    - Caretakers house Cornwell Farm, Thomas Peacock House, Undated
    - Mr. and Mrs. Vega, Undated
    - At Grange - Lion's Club Auction, Undated
    - Grange Park Lions Club Auction, Undated
    - Mr. and Mrs. O.K. Miller's 59th Anniversary, 1971 May 31
    - 24 Inch Snow, 1979 February 17-18
    - Great Falls Park, Undated
    - Great Falls Park, Undated
    - Negatives from Lt. Joseph A. Keranen, former head mounted police at Great Falls Park, Undated
    - Great Falls Grange, Undated
    - Campbell's Garage, Undated
    - Great Falls School, Undated
    - Alfred Leigh, Undated
    - Colvin Run School, Undated
    - Fitzgerald's Store, Undated
    - Ivan Money's House and George's View, Undated
    - O.K. Miller's Farm, 193 and Springvale (Fox Vale Farm), Undated
    - O.K. Miller's Farm, Undated
    - Alfred Leigh House, Undated
    - Andrew Chapel School, Undated
    - Mark Turner Farm, Undated
    - Thelma's, Undated
    - Old Great Falls Firehouse / Campbell's Auto Repair, Undated
    - Riverbend Sawmill, Undated
    - Campbell's Auto Repair, Undated
    - Old Building, Undated
    - Great Falls, Undated
    - Great Falls, Undated
    - Great Falls Park, Joe Keranen, Undated
    - Syd Follin Farm, Undated
    - Great Falls School, Undated
    - Melvin Thompson Pictures of 1936 Flood, Mrs. Beaver's School, teacher of Riverbend School, Undated
    - Iden/Gaskins House on Towlston Road, Undated
    - Sam Millard's Farm, Colvin Run Road, Undated
    - Roberts/Feighey House, Colvin Run, Undated
    - Daniel Cornwell's House, Route 193, Undated
    - Beavers House on Riverbend Road, Undated
    - Roberts/Mateer House, Colvin Run, Undated
    - Great Falls Firemen's Parade, 1960s
    - Money Family, Undated
    - Great Falls Cub Scouts Pinewood Derby, 1960s
    - Great Falls Thunderbirds Majorettes, Undated
    - Dranesville Tavern, Undated
    - Bill and Catherine Campbell's 40th Anniversary Party, Undated
    - O.K. Miller's Farm and Christmas Party at Fire Department, Undated
    - B.H. Buck Werner's Retirement Party, Undated
    - Grange, School, Firehouse, Undated
    - W.B. Harrison's, Undated
    - Thompson Family, Undated
    - Old Dominion Bridge, Undated
    - Children's Exhibits of Historical Places - Grange, Undated
    - Lord Bryan Fairfax, Cockrilles Store, Dr's Day house, Dr. Day, Difficult Run, Chain Bridge?, Bridge, Dunbarton, Firehouse for sale, Cornwell Mills and George Cornwell, Ish Family, Undated
    - Bradfords Barn, Undated
    - Cemetery at Spaulding Farm, Undated
    - Old Fire House, Thompson Family, Undated
    - Leigh House and Old Post Office, Undated
    - Cornwell Farm, Undated
    - John Buckner and Family, Sid Follin on horse, Undated
    - Mrs. Giarard and Jackson House, Undated
    - Jessie Smith and wife, Francis Rogers Ancestors, Lazaro, Parkview School and graduation class in D.C., Fla. Dolphin, Undated
    - Photos taken by Anne Bannerman, Undated
    - Unidentified negatives, Undated
  - Sub-series 8-3: Photo Albums, 1979-2001
    - GFHS Picnic, Harold Shaw's Mayfield, 1993 August
    - School Days, 1998 April 18
    - World War II Program, 1995
    - Great Falls Event (Maplewood-Ulfelder), Undated
    - Civil War at Colvin Run Mill, 1979
    - Cow Pie Bingo - Save the Turner Farm, 1997 July 4
    - Cedars Luncheon Historical Clothing, Undated
    - Church Folks, Undated
    - Great Falls Grange, Undated
    - Seniors at Cedars Luncheon, Undated
    - Miscellaneous Photos, Undated
    - Old Houses, 2000
    - Great Falls Center, 2000
    - Turner Farm, Undated
    - Thompson House - Walker Road, 2001
    - Story Book Farm, Undated
    - Pictures from Ralph Jackson (of Great Falls Park), Undated
    - Cornwell Farm, Undated
    - Burning, Mrs. Piggetts House, 1999
    - Great Falls Day 1999, 1999
    - Grange Day 2000, 2000
    - Great Falls Day 2000, 2000
    - Old School Days 1998, 1998
    - Potomac River Festival 1981, 1981
    - Great Falls Day 1999, 1999
    - Grange Day 1998, 1998
    - Grange Day 2000, 2000
    - GFHS Event, Undated
    - Riverbend Park, From Marion Reid, Undated
    - GFHS Event, Undated
    - Charles Calvin Walker, Undated
    - Cornwell, Undated
    - Homes, Undated
    - Library and a House, Undated
    - Hazel Sanders Thompson, Undated
    - Miscellaneous Photos, Undated
    - Brown/Van Patten Family, Undated
    - D.D. Cornwell House being moved (Bill Patram House Movers), Undated
    - Ann Cornwall Starke, Dr. Emory Starke Christmas Program GFHS, 1982
    - Cornwell Farm, Undated
    - D.D. Cornwell House after being moved, Undated
    - Crippin Family Photos, Undated
    - Jack Crippen's Dairy Cows, Undated
    - Dickey Family, Undated
    - Bob & Lucy's Housel's Cloverleaf Farm, Undated
    - Morgan Family, Undated
    - Pell Family Pictures of Cornwell Farm, Undated
    - Tucker and Reid Family, Undated
    - Marian Reid Collection, Undated
    - Tucker Family, Undated
    - Turner Family, Undated
    - Ulfelder Family, Undated
    - Wheeler Family, Undated
    - Wynkoop & Murphy House, Undated
    - White Pines Farm, Undated
    - Great Falls Library - Old and New, Undated
    - Great Falls & Old Dominion Railroad, Undated
    - Great Falls Park - High Water, Undated
    - Great Falls Park, Undated
    - Great Falls People, Undated
    - Stores, Undated
    - Great Falls Shopping Center, Undated
    - Great Falls Post Office - Last Day, Undated
    - Barns, Undated
    - Great Falls Fire Department, Undated
    - Houses, Undated
    - Cemetery Committee looking for Spaulding Cemetery, Undated
    - Photo Album, 1998 Grange and Old School Days, 1998 April
  - Sub-series 8-4: Photographs, 1979-1993
    - BALL-001 - Belle Ballenger, wife of Herbert Ballenger, standing with dog Shep. Ballenger farm on Utterback Store Road now Windermer subdivision., Undated
    - BALL-002 - Mrs. Ballenger. (duplicate), Undated
    - BARN-001 - Bradford's Barn, home of first fire engine and first ambulance., Undated
    - BARN-002 - Oliver's Barns on Georgetown Pike., Undated
    - BARN-008 - Oliver's Barn on Georgetown Pike across from present fire house, now the location of the Village Center., Undated
    - BRAD-001 - Norman F. (Day) Bradford, Sr., Undated
    - BRAD-002 - Group photo: Virgie Bradford, Carrie Wenzel, Sarah Johnson, Martha Cornwell., Undated
    - BRAD-003 - Vernon Bradford father of Norma, Sr., Jim, and Howard Bradford., Undated
    - BRAD-004 - L to R: Mrs. Norman F. (Edna) Bradford, Mr. and Mrs. John Buckner with Buckner children in front., Undated
    - BRAD-005 - Etta Bradford Cunningham grandmother of Norman Sr., Jim, and Howard Bradford., Undated
    - BRAD-007 - Etta Bradford Cunningham (second from left) and Lucy Brown (far right)., Undated
    - BREEDON-001 - Bill and Willie Breedon., Undated
    - BREEDON-002 - Bill Breedon at the Lions Club auction., Undated
    - BREEDON-003 - Willard Wood., Undated
    - CARP-001 - Lola Carpenter Leuchtenberger, Elizabeth Thompson, Herbert Ballenger (brother of Lilly Utterback), Frances Thompson, Buddy Thompson., Undated
    - CARP-002 - Catherine Carpenter (age 6) riding horse on Ballenger Farm on Utterback Store Road in 1926., Undated
    - CHURCH-001 - Brown's Chapel Church. Back row l to r: Edna Bradford and daughter, Vernon Bradford, Dot Jenkins. Front row l to r: Howard Cunningham and Herbert Brown., Undated
    - CHURCH-002 - Methodist Ministers at the Great Falls Camp meeting., Undated
    - CHURCH-003 - Sunday School Class at Forestville Methodist Church in 1940., Undated
    - CHURCH-004 - Probably a Sunday school group. L to R: Bertha Van Patton, unidentified, Florence Follin, Marie Schroy Dailey, Bessie Imdoden, Thelma Beach, Rosie Gunnell, Ann Cornwell, Catherine Follin Green., Undated
    - CHURCH-007 - Salem Methodist Protestant Church., Undated
    - CHURCH-009 - Moving Brown's Chapel, c. 1960s., Undated
    - CHURCH-010 - 85th birthday celebration and picnic for Herbert Brown at Brown's Chapel in 1940., Undated
    - CHURCH-011 - Bethel Primitive Baptist Church., Undated
    - CHURCH-013 - Pleasant Grove Methodist Church., Undated
    - CHURCH-015 - Dranesville Methodist Church., Undated
    - CHURCH-016 - Dranesville Church of the Brethren., Undated
    - CHURCH-017 - Dranesville Methodist Church., Undated
    - CHURCH-019 - Ruth Downs, Estelle Dailey, Frankie Winston and Martha "Matt" Martin, grandchildren of the founders of Smith Chapel United Methodist Church at the 75th anniversary celebration in July 1965., Undated
    - CHURCH-020 - Arnon Chapel, now a residence., Undated
    - CHURCH-032 - Arnon Methodist Church at Walker Road and Arnon Chapel Road. L to R: Elsie Goode, Phoebe Thomas (Mrs. Byron Thomas), Arthur Speight, Leland Hill, Harry Tavenner, Will Agin, Byron Thomas, Ellen Turner Jarvis, and Marie Robey., Undated
    - COATES-002 - Coates' Garage stood where the Exxon Station is now., Undated
    - COLMILL-006 - Addison Millard portrait. Ran Colvin Run Mill., Undated
    - COLMILL-007 - Emma Millard portrait. Ran Colvin Run Mill after her husband died, c. 1937., Undated
    - CORN-001 - Cornwell Farm before restoration, fireplace., Undated
    - CORN-002 - Cornwell Farm before restoration, c. 1937., Undated
    - CORN-003 - Entrance Hall after restoration, Cornwell Farm about 1937., Undated
    - CORN-004 - Cornwell Farm before restoration., Undated
    - CORN-005 - Cornwell Farm before restoration., Undated
    - CORN-006 - Entrance Hall before restoration, Cornwell Farm, c. 1936-1937., Undated
    - CORN-007 - Game room in Pell residence, Cornwell Farm, c. 1936-1937., Undated
    - CORN-008 - Guest room at Cornwell Farm after restoration about 1937., Undated
    - CORN-009 - Cornwell Farm before restoration., Undated
    - CORN-010 - Library at Cornwell Farm after restoration about 1937., Undated
    - CORN-011 - Owner's bedroom at Pell residence, Cornwell Farm after restoration about 1937., Undated
    - CORN-012 - Guest room at Pell residence, Cornwell Farm., Undated
    - CORN-013 - Dining room at Cornwell Farm after restoration about 1937., Undated
    - CORN-014 - Cornwell Farm during restoration and addition., Undated
    - CORN-015 - Cornwell Farm during restoration and addition., Undated
    - CORN-016 - Christmas card from Cornwell Farm., Undated
    - CORN-017 - Dining room at Cornwell Farm after restoration., Undated
    - CORN-018 - Cornwell Mills, grist mill on right, saw mill on left on west side of 10114 Georgetown Pike., Undated
    - CORN-023 - The Benjamin Frank Cornwell family. Back row: Newton, Henry, Charles, Jesse. Front row: Martha Cornwell (Pearson), Benjamin Franklin, Phebe. Mary Cornwell (Oliver), Harvey., Undated
    - CORN-024 - Henry O. Cornwell and wife Julia with granddaughter Blanche., Undated
    - CORN-025 - Ann Cornwell Starke speaking to the Great Falls Historical Society in December 1982 reading two chapters from her book "Grandpa's Shadow"., Undated
    - CORN-026 - Bessie and Harvey Cornwell with three of their children., Undated
    - CORN-027 - L to R: Sarah Elizabeth (Betty) Shelly Cornwell; Daniel David Cornwell; Martha G. Johnson Cornwell holding baby Paul Thomas Cornwell; Jesse Nally Cornwell. L to R: Annie Elizabeth Cornwell; George Cornwell; Cornelius Cornwell., Undated
    - CORN-028 - Jesse N. Cornwell celebrating 97th birthday with great-granddaughter Eddu J. Davis (Washington Post photo)., Undated
    - CORN-029 - Cornwell's Mills. Saw and grist mill operated by D.D. Cornwell., Undated
    - DICKEY-001 - Della, Ora, Minnie, Julia and James Dickey of Dickey's Inn., Undated
    - DICKEY-002 - James and Elizabeth Dickey, c. 1960s., Undated
    - DICKEY-003 - James and Elizabeth Dickey, c. 1960s., Undated
    - DICKEY-004 - Minnie Dickey, c. 1960s., Undated
    - DICKEY-005 - Mr. and Mrs. Elmer Dickey., Undated
    - DICKEY-006 - Horace Trammell and Will Dickey with unidentified women., Undated
    - DICKEY-007 - Alice Dickey, c. 1936-1937., Undated
    - DICKEY-021 - Bill Breedon with a banjo., Undated
    - FITZ-002 - M.D. Fitzgerald Store., 1979 April
    - FOLL-001 - Susie Follin mother of Sid Follin, Jr., c. 1967-1968., Undated
    - GFFD-003 - Great Falls Fire Department and equipment., 1986 November
    - GFFD-004 - Bingo stand on old carnival grounds now Village Centre., 1986 November
    - GFFD-005 - Firemen's Parade., Undated
    - GFFD-006 - Firemen's Parade, July 21, 1930., Undated
    - GFPARK-001 - Carl and Isabella Blaubock, proprietors of the Great Falls Tavern., Undated
    - GFPARK-002 - Lighthouse Harry Lee, founder of Matildaville., Undated
    - GFPARK-003 - Flood of 1936 or 1937 at Great Falls Park with 1st carousel in the background., Undated
    - GFPARK-005 - Private Joseph A. Keranen, U.S. Mounted Police on Banjo, the horse at Great Falls Park with Schmitz Tavern in background., Undated
    - GFPARK-011 - Train Station in Great Falls Park., Undated
    - GFPARK-013 - The second of two carousels at Great Falls Park, a Dentzel manufactured in 1900, was managed by Great Falls resident Gloria Follin., Undated
    - GFPARK-014 - The entrance to Great Falls Park showing the first Park Police office, the Great Falls Inn in the distance, and the Visitors Information building, c. 1960s., Undated
    - GFPARK-017 - Water in the Potomac Canal during flood., Undated
    - GFPARK-018 - Pavilion during the flood. Torn down 1987, pictured c. 1970s., Undated
    - GFPARK-021 - 2nd Merry Go Round at Great Falls Park., Undated
    - GFPARK-024 - Great Falls Park, c. 1960s., Undated
    - GFPARK-025 - Woman riding a horse in Great Falls Park., Undated
    - GFPARK-026 - Postcard copy of Great Falls Station, "Railroad Station, Great Falls, Va. 15 miles from Washington, D.C. on the Washington & Old Dominion Railway.", Undated
    - GFPARK-031 - Great Falls Inn., Undated
    - GFPARK-032 - 1st Great Falls Park carousel., Undated
    - GFPARK-033 - Low water at Great Falls Park, July 21, 1930., Undated
    - GFPARK-062 - Mounted park police building in Great Falls Park., Undated
    - GRANG-003 - National Grange Youth Department, 744 Jackson Pl., NW, Washington, D.C., Undated
    - GRANG-004 - [group in front of Grange], Undated
    - GRANG-005 - [group in front of Grange], Undated
    - GRANG-006 - [group in front of Grange], Undated
    - GRANG-007 - Lions Club Auction at the Grange., Undated
    - GRANG-008 - Lions Club Auction at the Grange., Undated
    - GRANG-009 - Ernest Gentry and William Breedon at Lions Club Auction at the Grange., Undated
    - GRANG-012 - Great Falls Grange members., Undated
    - GRANG-013 - Visitation of delegates of the Associated Country Women of the World, June 9, 1936., Undated
    - GTPIKE-001 - Georgetown Pike Toll Gate was located here. [This sign is part of the GFHS Collection and in the Oversize Drawer], Undated
    - GTPIKE-002 - Toll house on Route 193., 1980
    - GTPIKE-004 - Looking up Georgetown Pike from Ball's Store at Walker Road., Undated
    - GTPIKE-005 - Man riding by Methodist Church on Georgetown Pike., Undated
    - GUNN-001 - Gilbert Gunnell., Undated
    - HIRST-001 - Ella Hirst and Laura Presgraves., Undated
    - HOME-004 - Oliver House on Colvin Run Road., Undated
    - HOME-078 - House on Colvin Run Road., Undated
    - HOME-082 - House on hill at corner of Georgetown Pike and Leesburg Pike, now torn down., Undated
    - HOME-083 - Willard Woods house on Georgetown Pike., Undated
    - HOME-084 - The John Locke at 326 Walker Road was built by Barne and Sanders in 1872., Undated
    - JACK-001 - L to R: Wade Jackson, Charles Morris Jackson, Eva Trukett, Charles Morris Jackson Jr. (Casey), and Claude Jackson., Undated
    - JACK-002 - Jackson Farm on Riverbend Road near Georgetown Pike, c. 1940s., Undated
    - JACK-003 - Casey Jackson., Undated
    - JACK-004 - Casey Jackson., Undated
    - JACK-005 - Eppa H. Jackson., Undated
    - JACK-006 - Eppa Jackson., Undated
    - JACK-007 - Nell Adams Jackson., Undated
    - JACK-008 - Beatrice Bladen Jackson., Undated
    - JACK-009 - Eppa Jackson in office., Undated
    - JACK-010 - Andrew Jackson., Undated
    - JSMITH-002 - Jesse Smith (1818-1906)., 1993 February
    - MCCUTCH-001 - Homer McCutcheon was a blind broom maker lived at 600 Riverbend Road., Undated
    - MCCUTCH-002 - Homer McCutcheon with dog at 600 Riverbend Road., Undated
    - MCCUTCH-003 - Homer McCutcheon in 1921., Undated
    - MCCUTCH-004 - Lacy McCutcheon., Undated
    - MCKAY-001 - Shady Oak Store at Beach Mill Road and Walker Road., Undated
    - MILLER-001 - O.K. Miller, c. 1915., Undated
    - MONEY-001 - Mrs. Marion Money, Kathryn Harrison Farrar, and Iva Jenkins Donn Harrison., Undated
    - OLIVER-001 - Mildred Oliver, Lester Oliver, Evelyn Oliver and Austin Robinson standing on Georgetown Pike in front of store and house., Undated
    - POLAND-001 - Charlotte and Dale Poland, Utterback Store Road., Undated
    - RAIL-004 - Trolley in 1924., Undated
    - RAIL-006 - Great Falls and Old Dominion train coming off Aqueduct Bridge, left Arlington and Falls Church Railway Station on right. Capital Traction Station (Georgetown) in background., Undated
    - RAIL-007 - Forney-type engines like this one pulled first excursion trains to Great Falls Park., Undated
    - RECACT-003 - [Unidentified], Undated
    - REID-001 - Anna Reid sitting on car in 1921., Undated
    - REID-002 - Frankie Winston and children., Undated
    - RIVEB-001 - Bridge at River Bend Camp., Undated
    - SALEM-001 - Men serving in World War II honor roll from Salem Methodist Church., Undated
    - SAND-001 - H.P. Sanders, his neice Katherine Sanders now Carper, his mother Laurena Sanders and her mother Jane Folin by Church Camp Meeting tent., Undated
    - SCHOOL-006 - African American school on Walker Road., Undated
    - SCHOOL-037 - Forestville School class 1924 front row l to r: Lorena Rodgers, ?, Mildred Arnold, Clarence Goode, Raymond Holtzclaw, Rachel Wyant, May Shirkey, Teacher Gertrude Bazzle; 2nd row: George Oliver, Bernard Darne, Gladys Tucker, ?, Hazel Miller, Helen Miller; 3rd row: Albert Follin, Woodrow Poole, Marshall Daily, Dernest Daily, Wilbert Dailey, Lester O'Meara., Undated
    - STORE-008 - Jenkin's Store next to Dranesville with Jenkins family on porch., Undated
    - THEL-005 - Thelma's Store., Undated
    - TRAM-002 - Mr. Trammel with group of unidentified people., Undated
    - TUCKER-001 - Mrs. David Tucker (Bessie) and daughters Vivian and Lucy Tucker., Undated
    - TURNER-001 - Curt Turner mowing grass with horses. He drove the mules that pulled the barges on the C&O Canal., Undated
    - TURNER-002 - Horse and buggy with Mark Turner, Sr. next to the pony. (duplicated), Undated
    - TURNER-004 - Mark Turner Farm., Undated
    - TURNER-005 - Mark and Grace Turner on left with friends, c. 1935., Undated
    - TURNER-007 - Children of Mark and Connie Turner: Mark Turner III, Jean Lewin, and Susan Grace., Undated
    - TURNER-009 - Mark Turner, Jr. portrait., Undated
    - TURNER-013 - Grace and Mark Turner and friends at river., Undated
    - TURNER-014 - Group photo of the Turner family., Undated
    - TURNER-015 - Family photo with Mark Turner, Jr. in back row., Undated
    - TURNER-016 - Lewin family of McLean., Undated
    - TURNER-033 - Horse and buggy with Mark Turner, Sr. next to the pony., Undated
    - TURNER-049 - Association Countrywomen of the World in front of Great Falls Grange, June 9, 1936., Undated
    - WALKER-013 - Mazie Virginia Morgan with unidentified group., Undated
    - WERN-001 - Buck Werner receiving paper., Undated
    - WERN-007 - Buck's Store., Undated
    - WERN-014 - Buck's Country Store as an oriental rug store shortly before it was torn down., 1990 February
    - WERN-015 - Buck's Store., Undated
    - WHEEL-008 - Wheeler Mill., Undated
    - WODRR-003 - Train at Great Falls Station., Undated
    - WODRR-004 - Train at Great Falls Station. Carousel in background., Undated
  - Sub-series 8-5: Oversize Photographs, 1977-1980
    - BARN-003 - Barn on Route 7 near Trotting Horse Lane which use to be the Ponderosa Ride Stable., 1980
    - BARN-004 - Farm across Innsbruck Road from old school., 1977
    - BARN-005 - Barns at Hazelton Laboratories., 1980
    - BARN-006 - Brown's Barn at Colvin Run Road and Route 7., Undated
    - BARN-007 - Markdale Farm., Undated
    - BARN-009 - Mark Turner Farm., Undated
    - CHURCH-005 - Possibly a Sunday school picture from Salem Church. Virgie Wenzel (Bradford), Irene Wenzel, Les Lanham, Lemuel Wenzel, Susan Wenzel (Beach), Robert Lanham, Mark Turner Sr., Doll Rose Lanham, Fan Johnson, Lester Oliver., Undated
    - CHURCH-006 - Christmas pageant., Undated
    - CHURCH-021 - Great Falls United Methodist Church (1949), Undated
    - CHURCH-026 - Bethel Primitive Baptist Church on Route 7, organized in 1866., c. 1979-1980
    - CHURCH-027 - Dranesville Methodist Church. Part of the building was once a school., 1979 April
    - CHURCH-028 - At one time this was Turner's Dairy Barn then it was used as a dog kennel. After that it became St. Francis in the Field Episcopal Mission and is now Great Falls Episcopal Church., Undated
    - CHURCH-029 - Church of the Brethren., 1979 April
    - CHURCH-030 - Bethel Regular Baptist Church., Undated
    - CHURCH-031 - Forestville Methodist Church., 1979 April
    - COCKRILL-001 - Cockrill's Store and Post Office at Colvin Run now in Colvin Run Mill Park., c. 1978-1979
    - COLMILL-001 - The Miller's House at Colvin Run Mill., c. 1978-1979
    - COLMILL-002 - The Colvin Run Mill., c. 1978-1979
    - COLMILL-003 - Colvin Run Mill in 1939., Undated
    - COLMILL-004 - Millard's house before restoration at Colvin Run Mill., Undated
    - COLMILL-005 - Colvin Run Mill about 1900., Undated
    - CORN-019 - Harvey and Bessie Cornwell's House, Store and Post Office on the southeast corner of Georgetown Pike at Walker Road. Site of the Great Falls Shell Station., Undated
    - CORN-020 - Cornwell Farm, 9414 Georgetown Pike, after 1930 restoration., Undated
    - CORN-021 - The back of Cornwell Farm., Undated
    - CORN-022 - Ruins of the Cornwell Farm Grist Mill., 1978
    - DICKEY-001 - Dickey's Inn at Matildaville in Great Falls Park, May 22, 1931., Undated
    - DIFFR-001 - Great Falls and Old Dominion Railroad Bridge over Difficult Run on Old Dominion Drive. Built in 1906 and torn down in March 1979, 1979 February
    - DRANES-001 - 1940 Family Reunion at Dranesville Tavern, Sam and Catherine Jenkins with their children and spouses., Undated
    - DRANES-002 - The Dranesville Hotel (The Farr Tavern, not the Dranesville Tavern)., Undated
    - DRANES-003 - Dranesville Tavern before it was moved and restored, c. 1960., Undated
    - DRANES-004-005 - Dranesville Tavern., 1979 April
    - DRANES-006 - The Farr residence, store, school and post office at Dranesville. Very near to the left of Dranesville Tavern on Route 7., Undated
    - FOUR-001 - Osage orange trees in yard of Four Stairs., 1980 February 19
    - GFFD-007 - Group of people at Great Falls Fire Department Firemen Carnival, Undated
    - GFFD-008 - Firemen's Parade. Parade has just passed firehouse on right. Oliver's Barns in background, c. 1963., Undated
    - GFPARK-006 - Group of children posing in front of the falls at Great Falls Park., Undated
    - GFPARK-011 - Train Station in Great Falls Park., Undated
    - GFPARK-020 - 1st carousel at Great Falls Park from 1906 - c. 1942., Undated
    - GFPARK-022 - Second carousel in Great Falls Park [15 cent ticket pasted to photo], Undated